# **ROBERT QUAN**

Phone: 859-948-8361 Email: Rob.Quan@gmail.com GitHub: Github.com/TheRobQ Web: RobertQuan.com

Web Developer with a passion for creating applications that deliver clean, engaging user experiences. My background as a journalist + designer gives me a creative, collaborative approach to building applications.

# **Technical Skills** -

■ JavaScript

■ React

■ Node

■ Bootstrap

■ Responsive design

■ HTML5

■ jQuery

■ Express

■ API integration

■ .NET

■ CSS3

■ D3

■ SQL

■ Knex

■ Adobe Suite

# **Experience** -

## JavaScript Developer

September 2018 to Present

**Dimension Technology Solutions** 

- Develop web applications for clients including Chevron, Drummond and Valaris.
- Delivered enhancements including full-stack application that allows client to build troubleshooting flowcharts, API integrations, and developed numerous reusable components and utility classes for all clients
- Helped implement significant improvements in functionality to both front-end and .NET backend in C# for bespoke application used by Chevron's Salt Lake City Refinery. Improvements were instrumental in securing additional work from Chevron.
- One of two principal developers that delivered Android app used to schedule maintenance and projects for off-shore rigs.

## Support Engineer

Tiny Technologies | TinyMCE

May 2018 to September 2018

- Support: Troubleshoot front-end code and answer implementation questions for TinyMCE clients in a variety of frameworks.
- Evangelism: Reach out to open source community, answer questions on Stackoverflow, create learning materials for developers including a series of Webinars showing how to initialize and configure TinyMCE and use it in frameworks such as React or Vue.
- Development: Test readability of documentation by implementing new features based only on provided documents as written.

# **Assistant Web Development Instructor**

University of Denver

March 2018 to August 2018

- Helped lead instructor teach MERN stack (Mongo, Express, React, Node) to aspiring developers in the University of Denver's part-time web development program.
- Helped students with core concepts relating to JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3 and React and helped troubleshoot students' code.

## **Design Director**

August 2012 to October 2017

Digital First Media | Prairie Mountain Media

- Managed an award-winning team of 24 designers.
- Oversaw design, editing and production for 12 newspapers including the Denver Post, Boulder Daily Camera, and St. Paul Pioneer Press.
- Under my direction, we expanded production from 4 client sites to 12 client sites and grew the team from 9 designers and editors to 24.
- Coordinated with advertising and marketing departments across 12 client sites

# Past Web Development Contracts —

#### Rocky Mountain Puppy Rescue: Current

- Worked with Rocky Mountain Puppy Rescue pro bono to overhaul their site.
- Transitioned org to a Wix solution, transferring all content and integrating their current form solutions into their new CMS.
- Currently working with Rocky Mountain Puppy Rescue pro bono to perform maintenance and ensure their site stays up to date.

#### TrifectaKY: Jan. 2018

- Created Node/Express server that integrates with the GDAX API and returns client's account data and Cryptocurrency rates.
- Worked with client to automate trades via GDAX API based on parameters provided by client and creating Mocha/Chai tests.

#### Worthy-Works: Feb. 2018

- Created new page for client's web site that integrates Full Contact API. Users type email and get back associated LinkedIn URL.
- Delivered Google Script that integrates Sheets with Full Contact API and performs batch search for LinkedIn profiles based on emails.

#### Katorishintoryu-usa.org: April 2018

- Created an informational, mobile responsive website for a local martial arts school.
- Working with client to ensure site is placed on Google search

# Education ————

Galvanize Web Development Immersive | B.A. English, University of Kentucky